You are one of
the Seafolk, correct?
What if I am?
You must be another soldier...
I am here to eliminate you.
Was that...
the last of them?
Wow!
- Awesome!
- Amazing!
They must have been desperate.
Now I'm angry.
I will tear you to shreds.
I let my guard down again.
I never learn.
Saitama...
You're Class C, rank 2.
Are you sure?
Yeah.
Hurry it up. It's raining.
He burst through every record
during the fitness exam...
And he worked with some Class S
heroes to destroy that meteor.
But because he came out of nowhere,
people are saying he's a fraud.
Any other class C hero I'd stop...
This may be our chance to see
how strong he truly is.
Saitama, here's the location.
Head there immediately.
UNYIELDING JUSTICE
One punch
Three, two, one, kill shot
sanjou, hisshou, shijou saikyou
He joins the fight, he wins, the strongest in history
nan datten da, frustration
Are you talking to him? Frustration ☹
ore wa tomaranai
He's not going to stop
one punch, kanryou, rensenrenshou
One punch, that's it, one fight after another
ore wa katsu, tsune ni katsu, asshou
He wins, he always wins, overwhelmingly
power, get power
Power, get power
girigiri genkai made
On to the very edge
Hero
ore o tataeru koe ya
There are voices praising him
kassai nante hoshiku wa nai sa
but he's not doing this for acclaim
Hero
dakara hitoshirezu aku to tatakau
So he just fight evil without end
Nobody knows who he is
sora ooi oshiyoseru teki
Enemies to fight are numerous as the stars
\OP Sync Point - Smiley Star, First Frame}
ore wa se wo muke wa shinai
and he's not gonna turn his back on you
Hero
naraba yuruginaki kakugo shita tame
He's made up his mind and ain't gonna yield
tatakau hero
A fighting hero
kodoku na hero
A lone hero
I
i wanna be a saikyou hero
I wanna be the strongest hero
Those who can walk,
leave the shelter now!
I cannot promise I will win.
Run, while I keep him busy!
None of you monkeys
will escape me!
Lightning Eye!
I can't see...
Machinegun Blows!
You do like combo attacks,
don't you?
You can do it!
Quiet!
Now you melt, girl.
If you'd focused on me,
you could have easily dodged
my little ball of acid.
Instead, you chose to
sacrifice yourself to save a runt.
You're a fool, but I give you credit
for giving me a few scratches.
Of course, they've already healed.
Now, die.
Justice Crash!!
The Cyclist for Justice,
Mumen Rider is here!
The top hero in Class C?
D-Don't...
It's Mumen Rider!
Mumen Rider came for us.
But he...
I'm bored already.
Oh, my apologies.
I nearly forgot to kill you.
Justice Tackle...
No one expects much—
...from me.
They think a Class C hero
won't be much help.
I know that better than anyone!
I'm not good enough for Class B.
I'm weak. I know that much.
No one has to tell me I have
no chance of beating you.
I already... know that!
What are you babbling about?
Begging for your life?
And yet, I must try.
It's not about winning or losing!
It's about me taking you on
right here, right now!
Enough of your rambling.
Time to finish you off.
You can do it!
Mumen Rider, you can do it!
You're the Cyclist for Justice!
Beat that weird monster, beat him!
You can do it!
Yeah, get him!
Beat him up!
We're counting on you, Mumen Rider.
- You can do it!
- Beat him!
Good luck!
I think not!
You did fine. Nice fight.
Yet another piece of garbage
washed up on my shore?
H-Hey, Genos!
Are you still alive?!
Mas...ter...
Hang on for a second.
I've gotta pound this Seafreak
or whatever it's called.
I heard that!
Impressive. You're still on your feet
after one of my punches.
Clearly you're different
from the rest of this trash.
Huh? Your punch was
too weak, that's all.
Hey, someone else is over there.
Who is that? A hero?
That head...
I remember it from
the Hero Registry.
I know him! He's a Class C rookie.
I think he's Rank 2.
Class C?
So we're still gonna get killed...
But that punch
didn't hurt him at all.
That's your imagination.
You saw how many heroes
were blown away
by that thing's punches, right?
I am the King of the Deep,
Lord of the Seas.
All life on Earth comes from the sea,
as if she were our mother.
In other words, as ruler of the seas,
I am the pinnacle of a pyramid
that includes every living
organism on this world!
To defy me, means
Yeah, yeah, I got it.
It's raining out, so let's do this.
Whaattt!!
Awesome!
That was amazing!
- Thank goodness!
- He did it!
Well... that was lame.
I kinda had my hopes up, too.
I'm back with my weapons.
But damn you, Deep Sea King.
You got away.
Hey, what's that?
It is the mail.
The post office cannot come here,
so the drone now delivers the mail.
The post office's drone?
No, it belongs to
the Hero Association.
I see.
The public sends these to the heroes,
much like fan letters.
Seriously? Are there any for me?
- There are.
-Oh! Let's go in and open them!
TO C CLASS HERO SAITAMA
- Oh! Let's go in and open them!
m -122 -123 l 187 -125 l 146 -30 l 167 -13 l 194 -18 l 261 -17 l 301 19 l 283 76 l 280 135 l 289 199 l 279 272 l -117 270 l -102 130 l -122 -124
Mr. Genos,
I've been a huge fan of
yours since i first laid eyes on you!
I think you are a true hero.
I even joined your fan club!
I'm just crazy about you!
No one cares about you!
You Cowardly, Cheating Bastard
Damn it. I'll find out who sent it.
Here's a guy with free time.
All it took was one punch!
One punch! Just one!
Is he really Class C?
He's too strong!
Or maybe...
...the monster wasn't really that tough?
Yeah, but so many heroes went down.
That just means those
heroes were weaklings.
Maybe... I suppose the monster didn't
look all that tough when he killed it.
After all, a Class C hero
took it out with a single punch!
What's that say about
the heroes it beat?
They may call themselves
Class A or Class S,
but their titles don't mean a thing.
Hey, enough of that.
They risked their lives for us.
Risked their lives?
Anyone can do that.
But a "hero" has to beat monsters.
It all ended well this time,
so whatever.
But it's annoying when heroes
who are really just average Joes
show up and try to save you.
If you're gonna call yourself
a hero, then—
Shut your fat mouth!
Why are you getting mad at me?
The Hero Association gets their funds
from our donations, right?
As long as we're paying for it,
they'd better protect us.
The fact of the matter is
that bald guy pretty much took
care of it all by himself.
So all the other heroes
died for nothing.
Anyone can come up with a way
to buy a little time.
In the end, the other "heroes"
didn't do anything heroic.
I said shut up!
We were all saved.
Just leave it at that.
Exactly!
Today's my lucky day!
The other heroes wore the monster down,
so beating it was kid's play!
Good thing I was late.
I barely did a thing and now
I get all the credit.
Hey, spread the word, all of you!
I'm the one who finished
the monster off!
I'll beat the snot out
of anyone who says
it's only 'cause I got here late!
What's he mean?
The monster was already weak?
Huh...?
Hang on a sec. That's Saitama!
Saitama?
He's the hero from City Z
that everyone calls a cheat.
What? A cheat?
He appeared out of nowhere
and climbed the ranks super-fast.
Yeah, pretty fishy.
Hey, you guys!
Look after the fallen heroes, okay?
If they die on me,
how am I gonna cash in
on their work?
He is a cheat!
Man, that's no fair.
So he's just taking the credit?
Compared to him, the other heroes
seem a little more heroic.
Where would we be now...
if the other heroes hadn't fought?
Yeah, I feel so grateful to them all...
Master Saitama...
Is this really what you want?
Hey, it stopped raining.
If this is the path you choose to walk,
I will not interfere.
But in the future, if you are ever
forced into a corner by this,
at that moment, I will—
Hey, there's one more.
To the hero Saitama
Thanks!!
Someone's thanking me.
It must be someone you saved.
I see. Any left?
There is one from the Hero Association.
The Association?
Are they firing me?
Well, whatever.
What's this? I'm Class C...rank 1?
CITY Z - HERO ASSOCIATION OFFICE
So, why'd you call me in?
When you registered with
the Hero Registry,
you were given
the Association handbook.
Haven't you read it?
It lists all our rules and regulations.
Yeah, I guess I've got it somewhere.
No matter. Congratulations on
attaining rank 1 in Class C.
Hm? Oh, I see.
So you guys are the ones
who decide the hero rankings.
There are more members
on the review board,
but the four of us here today
will be handling your interview.
Interview?
The top ranking Class C hero is given
the option to be promoted to Class B.
However, if you wish to remain
in Class C, that's fine too.
How about it, Mr. Saitama?
Do you want to move up?
Although if you do, you'll be ranked
at the very bottom again.
Either way's fine,
but I guess I'll try moving up.
There'll be no more
weekly quotas that way.
Besides, I can't stick to Class C
forever with Genos in Class S.
I see, so you want a promotion.
First, we'll need you to
answer some questions
and undergo a psychiatric analysis.
This Saitama...
He's the one who finished off
the Deep Sea King.
What do you think?
Some say he's a fraud...
He set new overall records
in the fitness exam,
so his physical ability is solid.
Well, according to rumors,
he cheated on the exams, too.
Rumors are just rumors.
No sense in doubting him now.
The bottom line is,
he wants to move up.
Why not let him go for now?
If he's for real,
he'll make it in Class B.
But if he's a fake, he'll soon regret it.
He is entering a cruel and callous world.
We'll cross that bridge when we must.
Promotion to Class B?
You interrupted my filming for this?
It's not something that
needs my attention.
This is a decision for
the executive committee.
Listen.
I only want input on managing
heroes Class A and above,
since they have a strong impact on society.
As a hero in the same class,
if they're inadequate,
it hurts my image too.
Especially this last incident...
It was beyond inadequate—
it was appalling.
Don't you agree?
Speaking of social impact,
the hero now wanting to move up
is the one who finished off
the Deep Sea King.
UNKNOWN HEROES SNATCH VICTORY
Why the sour pusses?
That's no way to show off
those cute faces!
You?!
I thought you were in prison!
I escaped just to see you!
Now... It's time for your Angel shots!
You guys! You need your meds!
A CLASS S FAILURE!!
So I'm Class B now...
Those tests took long enough.
Meh, not like I had to be somewhere.
Something smells good...
Welcome.
Assorted oden, please.
All right.
Want a drink?
If you're not drinking,
let me buy you a plate.
Why?
That.
You were at the Association?
Let's celebrate your promotion.
Thanks
for giving me a ride.
Should I walk?
N-No... I can handle it...
Hey, are you scared?
You got separated from
the Class S hero, Genos, right?
The enemy is threat level Demon.
A monster so formidable that even if
the Class S and Class B heroes all
ganged up on him, they'd never win.
So if you wanna run...
Are you Class S too?
No, I'm Class C.
Laugh if you want to.
I'm not laughing.
It sure is tough making those
weekly quotas for us Class C's...
You're a funny guy.
I'm Mumen Rider.
A hero, just like you.
Huh?
Hey! Watch it!
Oh! You're that guy!
I've been looking for you.
I couldn't say everything
in my letter.
Oh yeah.
Maybe some mozuku then?
Hey! Give us your best mozuku!
Comin' right up.
\ED}
Hey, come back home soon
On nights when the new moon shivers from my sighs
I close my eyes and think of you
I want to see you... I feel like crying
I feel so romantic
I hope these feelings reach you
\Sync Point - 2 Weed leaves on the floor, First Frame}
I know very well
how hard you work all the time
You're the one I love
You're so strong but I'm still worried
Don't hide your weakness, at least show it to me
I'll find you before any stars
Come straight back home
Hey, come back home soon
It...it approaches!
Madame Shibabawa?
What's wrong?
A violent catastrophe draws near...
Madame Shibabawa!
Get a hold of yourself!
This is the end!
The Earth is doomed!
NEXT
Episode
UNPARALLELED PERIL
Eh? What is this place?
I am the Deep Sea King!
If I made one misstep, it was
not fighting the battle at sea.
An away game!
If we'd fought at sea,
things would be different!
Next time on One-Punch Man:
Episode 10, "Unparalleled Peril."
Really? There's something even
more dangerous than me?